irishnews.com 2009-10-19

# The Irish News - Online Newspaper for Ireland - irishnews.com

HOME | PRIVACY STATEMENT >

The Irish News takes the privacy of its users seriously. We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our users while providing a personalised and valuable service. This Privacy Policy Statement explains the data processing practices of irishnews.com. If you have any requests concerning your personal information or any queries with regard to these practices please contact our Privacy Officer by e-mail at internet@irishnews.com  
Information collected Personal information is collected by Irish News Limited. We collect personal information from you through the use of the registration and subscription forms and every time you e-mail us your details.

We also collect information automatically about your visit to our site. The information obtained in this way, which includes demographic data and browsing patterns, is only used in aggregate form.

Use and Disclosure of personal information We process personal information collected via irishnews.com for the purposes of:  
• providing a personalised service  
• conducting market research surveys  
• running competitions and  
• providing you with information about products and services we and other companies offer.  
We also use information in aggregate form (so that no individual user is identified):  
• to build up marketing profiles  
• to aid strategic development  
• to manage our relationship with advertisers and  
• to audit usage of the site.

Use of cookies We use "cookies" to identify you when you visit the irishnews.com site and to build up a demographic profile.  
A cookie is a small piece of information sent by a web server to a web browser, which enables the server to collect information back from the browser. Find out more about the use of cookies on [http://www.cookiecentral.com](http://www.cookiecentral.com/)

Our use of cookies also allows registered users to be presented with a personalised version of the site.  
Internet-based transfers Given that the Internet is a global environment, using the Internet to collect and process personal data necessarily involves the transmission of data on an international basis. Therefore, by browsing the irishnews.com site and communicating electronically with us you acknowledge and agree to our processing of personal data in this way.

"We use a third-party advertising company to serve ads when you visit our website.  
This company may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visit to this Web site in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you.  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.  
If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by this company, please click here :  
<http://www.doubleclick.net/us/corporate/privacy>

For further information contact:

**Ruairí ONeill**  
Web Designer  

**Michael Mathews**  
Junior Web Designer
